You married him
Didn't Mr. Gu also keep reminding everyone
that you chose Su Yurou
for the future of both families
Mr. Fu, today is the Su and
Gu families' internal meeting
It involves my wife
so I'm not an outsider
Mingyao, please have a seat
As expected, the agreement from my past life is back
Look at this first
Now we need you to continue
fulfilling your guarantee promise
and stabilize the project
Sign it and cooperate with the statement
and the project won't be affected
Sister
The project involves many employees
and the reputation of both families
You can't just ignore it because you're upset
When did I say I'd ignore the project
I just don't want to guarantee
a problematic contract anymore
Then let's just stick to the contract
It clearly states here
the guarantee is limited to Phase 1 actual construction expenses
Right
That's right
But the use of funds here has already
expanded under Gu's name